[
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many teams typically participate in F1 races each season?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "8",
      "12",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many drivers are typically in a standard F1 race?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "24",
      "18",
      "26"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many standard F1 races are currently on the schedule?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "10",
      "16",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How long does a standard F1 race generally last?",
    "correctAnswer": "2 hours",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1 hour",
      "3 hours",
      "4 hours"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How many points are awarded for 1st place in a standard F1 race?",
    "correctAnswer": "25 points",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "30 points",
      "20 points",
      "50 points"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many drivers are awarded points per race?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "20",
      "15",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What trophy is awarded to the top point-scoring driver each season?",
    "correctAnswer": "F1 World Drivers' Championship Trophy",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "FIA Championship Racing Trophy",
      "F1 Driver Trophy",
      "F1 World Drivers' Cup"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What trophy is awarded to the most winning team each season?",
    "correctAnswer": "F1 World Constructors' Championship Trophy",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "World Champion Drivers' Cup",
      "World Manufacturer's Championship",
      "Constructors Cup"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Over how many days does an F1 race weekend extend?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How much time is allotted for each pre-race Free Practice session?",
    "correctAnswer": "1 hour",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1.5 hours",
      "2 hours",
      "2.5 hours"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the 1st position on the starting grid called?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pole",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Grid",
      "Front",
      "Start"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag is used for caution such as a minor accident or debris on the track?",
    "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Red",
      "Orange",
      "White"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag indicates the track is clear and racing can resume?",
    "correctAnswer": "Green",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "White",
      "Blue",
      "Orange"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How many qualifying stages determine pole positions?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the minimum number of pit-stops required per standard race?",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 team uses the prancing horse logo?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ferrari",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Mercedes",
      "Alpine",
      "McLaren"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What nationality is Fernando Alonso?",
    "correctAnswer": "Spanish",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Portuguese",
      "Mexican",
      "Italian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which country hosts the Suzuka Grand Prix?",
    "correctAnswer": "Japan",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "China",
      "Saudi Arabia",
      "Spain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team is associated with the color papaya orange?",
    "correctAnswer": "McLaren",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Red Bull",
      "Aston Martin",
      "Audi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which circuit was added to the F1 calendar in 2023?",
    "correctAnswer": "Las Vegas",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Miami",
      "Jeddah (Saudi Arabia)",
      "Qatar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What drink is traditionally consumed on the podium after an F1 win?",
    "correctAnswer": "Champagne",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Prosecco",
      "Sparkling Wine",
      "Franciacorta"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which country is Lando Norris from?",
    "correctAnswer": "United Kingdom",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Australia",
      "Austria",
      "Italy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "For which team does Isack Hadjar currently drive?",
    "correctAnswer": "Racing Bulls",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Haas",
      "Williams",
      "Alpine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver replaced Lewis Hamilton at Mercedes in 2025?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kimi Antonelli",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ollie Bearman",
      "Liam Lawson",
      "Franco Colapinto"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver is famously recognized by his blonde mullet?",
    "correctAnswer": "Valtteri Bottas",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Sebastian Vettel",
      "Kevin Magnussen",
      "Alex Albon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many F1 race circuits are in the United States?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which F1 driver has had the longest F1 career?",
    "correctAnswer": "Fernando Alonso",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Kimi Raikkonen",
      "Rubens Barrichello"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver is known by fans as “Smooth Operator”",
    "correctAnswer": "Carlos Sainz",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Fernando Alonso",
      "Charles Leclerc",
      "George Russell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What do drivers stand on after a race to receive trophies?",
    "correctAnswer": "Podium",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Box",
      "Mount",
      "Platform"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 team is owned by a major energy drink company?",
    "correctAnswer": "Red Bull",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Alpine",
      "McLaren",
      "Kick Sauber"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 team is headquartered in Silverstone, UK and races in green?",
    "correctAnswer": "Aston Martin",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Haas",
      "Williams",
      "Racing Bulls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": " What is the term used when a driver wins a race from pole position, sets the fastest lap, and leads every lap",
    "correctAnswer": "Grand Slam",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Triple Crown",
      "360",
      "Hat Trick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who won the first (2023) Las Vegas Grand Prix?",
    "correctAnswer": "Max Verstappen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Charles Leclerc",
      "Lando Norris",
      "George Russell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which rookie American driver joined Williams for the 2023 season?",
    "correctAnswer": "Logan Sargeant",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jack Doohan",
      "Lance Stroll",
      "Kevin Magnussen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What nationality is driver Lance Stroll?",
    "correctAnswer": "Canadian",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "American",
      "French",
      "Hungarian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What term is used to reference the shorter race held on some Saturdays that awards points and affects grid position?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sprint",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Heat",
      "Shootout",
      "Qualifier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What does it mean when a driver is told \"box box box\" during a F1 race?",
    "correctAnswer": "They are being called in for a pit stop",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "They are about to be boxed in by another car",
      "Something is wrong and they need to retire their car",
      "The team is about to communicate details over team radio"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which racing tire supplier is currently used in F1?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pirelli",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Michelin",
      "Goodyear",
      "Firestone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver is known as the ‘Honey Badger”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Daniel Ricciardo",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lando Norris",
      "Alexander Albon",
      "Max Verstappen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the stat for the quickest single lap recorded by a F1 driver during a race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Fastest Lap",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Speed Lap",
      "Quickest Lap",
      "Top Lap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which of these is NOT a F1 pit crew job during a race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Refueler",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jack Man",
      "Car Stabilizer",
      "Front Wing Adjuster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the name of the all-female motor racing championship series founded by the FIA?",
    "correctAnswer": "F1 Academy",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Women in Racing",
      "F3 Academy",
      "FIA  Academy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which of these is NOT a current F1 Team?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lamborghini",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ferrari",
      "McLaren",
      "Aston Martin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 1,
    "levelName": "Rookie",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What breed is Charles Leclerc's dog (Leo)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dachshund",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Bull Dog",
      "Jack Russell",
      "Corgie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the total number of points awarded across the board for each standard F1 race?",
    "correctAnswer": "101 points",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "100 points",
      "210 points",
      "80 points"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What race strategy involves pitting earlier to gain time on fresher tires and leapfrog a rival?",
    "correctAnswer": "Undercut",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Pit-First",
      "Flanking",
      "Stealth Pass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which Grand Prix was canceled mid-race in 2023 due to flooding and safety concerns?",
    "correctAnswer": "Imola",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Cota",
      "Madring",
      "Miami"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver won a Grand Prix in 2020 despite standing in for another driver due to COVID?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sergio Perez",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Carlos Sainz",
      "Pietro Fittipaldi ",
      "Nico Hulkenberg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team raced with the slogan “The Power of Dreams”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Honda",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Red Bull",
      "McLaren",
      "Benetton"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the fastest F1 recorded pit-stop for tire changes?",
    "correctAnswer": "1.80 seconds",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2.01 seconds",
      "2.25 seconds",
      "1.94 seconds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag is used to stop a race due to a dangerous situation?",
    "correctAnswer": "Red",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Orange",
      "Black",
      "Yellow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag indicates the end of a race or practice session?",
    "correctAnswer": "Checkered",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "White",
      "Black",
      "Blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the F1 term for the period when there's a lot of speculation surrounding driver contracts and team changes? ",
    "correctAnswer": "Silly Season",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Summer Season",
      "Rumor Season",
      "Scuttle Season"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the F1 governing organization called?",
    "correctAnswer": "FIA",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "FIFA",
      "IMSA",
      "NASCAR"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "During how many months of the year are F1 races generally held?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How long in distance is a sprint race?",
    "correctAnswer": "1/3 of a full race",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1/4 of a full race",
      "1/2 of a full race",
      "2/3 of a full race"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the final pre-race lap on race day called?",
    "correctAnswer": "Formation Lap",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Reconnaissance Lap",
      "Qualifying Lap",
      "Flying Lap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many types of wet and dry tires are available for F1 races?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What term is used for the judges and referees for F1 race sessions?",
    "correctAnswer": "Stewards",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Paddock Judge",
      "Clockers",
      "Marshals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which driver has the most pole positions in history?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lewis Hamilton",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Michael Schumacher",
      "Sebestian Vettel",
      "Ayrton Senna"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is the youngest driver to win an F1 race to date?",
    "correctAnswer": "Max Verstappen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Kimi Antonelli",
      "Oscar Piastri",
      "Lewis Hamilton"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What are the maximum points a driver can earn over a single weekend?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "25",
      "20",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver is known as Checo?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sergio Perez",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Carlos Sainz",
      "Charles Leclerc",
      "Liam Lawson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which new constructor enters F1 in the 2026 season?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cadillac",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Porsche",
      "Tesla",
      "Jaguar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver famously drank from his shoe after winning races?",
    "correctAnswer": "Daniel Ricciardo",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lando Norris",
      "Kimi Raikkonen",
      "Ollie Bearman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is the current team principal for Williams Racing?",
    "correctAnswer": "James Vowles",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Toto Wolff",
      "Christian Horner",
      "Andy Cowell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver scored a podium as a 2023 rookie with McLaren?",
    "correctAnswer": "Oscar Piastri",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Kimi Antonelli",
      "Logan Sargeant",
      "Nick de Vries"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who was the first Thai driver to ever stand on the F1 podium?",
    "correctAnswer": "Alex Albon",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Yuki Tsunoda",
      "Prince Bira",
      "Zhou Guanyu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver was known early in his career as ‘Mr. Saturday’?",
    "correctAnswer": "George Russell",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Nico Hulkenberg",
      "Yuki Tsunoda",
      "Pierre Gasly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How many F1 World Championships did Fernando Alonso win?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who are the unpaid safety volunteers that monitor track incidents?",
    "correctAnswer": "Marshals",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Stewards",
      "EMTs",
      "Runners"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team has competed in every season of the F1 World Championship since its inception?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ferrari",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "McLaren",
      "Williams",
      "Mercedes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many types of slick tires can drivers choose from?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What role leads, manages, and represents an F1 team, both operationally and strategically, across all aspects of the sport?",
    "correctAnswer": "Team Principal",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Chief Engineer",
      "Technical Director",
      "Chief Mechanic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver was the first to go through the Honda Formula Dream Program?",
    "correctAnswer": "Yuki Tsunoda",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Zhou Guanyu",
      "Alex Albon",
      "Ayumu Iwasa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the maximum penalty an F1 driver can receive?",
    "correctAnswer": "Race Ban",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Retirement",
      "Grid Drops",
      "Penalty Points on License"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What car number has Lewis Hamilton used for most of his F1 career?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1",
      "14",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the name of the starting position grid line that the pole-sitter lines up on?",
    "correctAnswer": "P1",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "G1",
      "SP1",
      "F1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the term used when a driver finishes among the top 10 in a race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Points Finish",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Pack Finish",
      "Scorer",
      "Finisher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What company owns F1?",
    "correctAnswer": "Liberty Media",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "FIA",
      "Delta Topco",
      "International Motorsports Assoc. "
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What year was the first F1 race held?",
    "correctAnswer": "1950",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "1940",
      "1954",
      "1962"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver achieved his first podium finish ever after 239 race starts?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nico Hulkenberg",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Felipe Massa",
      "David Coulthard",
      "Adrian Sutil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag gives drivers a warning for unsportsmanlike behavior?",
    "correctAnswer": "Black and White",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Orange and White",
      "Black and Blue",
      "Blue and Yellow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What cars do the F1 Academy drivers drive?",
    "correctAnswer": "Formula 4 level cars",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Formula 3 level cars",
      "Formula Junior cars",
      "Formula E cars"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which F1 driver holds the record for the fastest recorded top speed during a F1 race (231 mph)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Valtteri Bottas",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Sergio Perez"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the name of the F1 car part that gives downforce and looks like a wing?",
    "correctAnswer": "Rear Wing",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Diffuser",
      "Spoiler",
      "Exhaust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is a chicane?",
    "correctAnswer": "A sequence of tight turns designed to slow cars down",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "A long, high-speed straight section of track",
      "A steep hill climb followed by a sharp descent",
      "A type of pit lane speed control system"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which driver holds the record for the fastest lap in F1 history (average speed of 164.466 mph)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Max Verstappen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Fernando Alanso",
      "Valtteri Bottas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 2,
    "levelName": "Midfielder",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the record for the highest number of red flags issued during a full F1 qualifying session?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which track is known for the tightest pit entry in Formula 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "Baku",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "COTA (Texas)",
      "Yas Marina (Abu Dhabi)",
      "Las Vegas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver finished 2nd in the 2008 championship by just one point, despite winning more races than the champion?",
    "correctAnswer": "Felipe Massa",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Fernando Alonso",
      "Jenson Button"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which of these issues would NOT incur a driver penalty during the race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Electronic System Failure",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Loose Wheel",
      "Speeding in the Pit Lane",
      "Unsafe Release"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What does it indicate when a F1 driver's sector time during a session is displayed in purple?",
    "correctAnswer": "Fastest of all drivers in a specific sector",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Slowest of all drivers in a specific sector",
      "Personal best time in a specific sector",
      "Track record in a specific sector"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which brand of champagne is currently used for the F1 podium celebrations?",
    "correctAnswer": "Moet & Chandon",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Veuve Clicquot",
      "Dom Perignon",
      "Ferrari Trento"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What type of tire would be used for a damp track with light water?",
    "correctAnswer": "Intermediate",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Wet",
      "Hard",
      "Medium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the term for the process where tire rubber gets deposited on the racing line which can improve tire grip?",
    "correctAnswer": "Rubbering-in",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Run-Off",
      "Gripping",
      "Evolution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What are the small pieces of rubber that generally accumulate off the racing line most often called?",
    "correctAnswer": "Marbles",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Pellets",
      "Tire Boogers",
      "Loose Stuff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What does a blue flag mean in F1 racing?",
    "correctAnswer": "A faster car is approaching; let them pass",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Rain is coming",
      "Overtaking is not allowed",
      "Pit lane is closed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What are the most F1 World Championships won by a single driver?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What year did Max Verstappen win his first F1 World Championship?",
    "correctAnswer": "2021",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2022",
      "2023",
      "2024"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver was inspired from age 3 to start go-kart racing by the Pixar movie Cars? ",
    "correctAnswer": "Liam Lawson",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Gabriel Bortoleto",
      "Ollie Bearman",
      "Isack Hadjar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What team did Daniel Ricciardo join after leaving Red Bull?",
    "correctAnswer": "Renault",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Alpine",
      "Williams",
      "Audi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver earned the nickname ‘Iceman’?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kimi Raikkonen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Kevin Magnussen",
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Ayrton Senna"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team did Max Verstappen debut with in F1?",
    "correctAnswer": "Toro Rosso",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ferrari",
      "Haas",
      "Renault"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What country did Robert Kubica represent?",
    "correctAnswer": "Poland",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Hungary",
      "Netherlands",
      "Italy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who was the youngest driver to win an F1 race for Ferrari?",
    "correctAnswer": "Charles Leclerc",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Niki Lauda",
      "Kimi Raikkonen",
      "Alain Prost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is the youngest British driver to achieve an F1 podium finish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lando Norris",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Oliver Bearman",
      "George Russell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver is the son of a two-time World Rally Champion?",
    "correctAnswer": "Carlos Sainz",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Damon Hill",
      "Nico Rosberg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "How many years did Lewis Hamilton race for Mercedes?",
    "correctAnswer": "12 years",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "8 years",
      "10 years",
      "14 years"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is the youngest driver ever to lead a Formula 1 race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kimi Antonelli",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Robert Kubica",
      "Sebastian Vettel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who scored points on his F1 debut in 2024 as a stand-in driver for Ferrari?",
    "correctAnswer": "Oliver Bearman",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Issac Hadjar",
      "Franco Colapinto",
      "George Russell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What year were Sprint races introduced to the F1 calendar?",
    "correctAnswer": "2021",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2020",
      "2019",
      "2018"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag disqualifies a driver requiring a return to the pit?",
    "correctAnswer": "Black",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Yellow",
      "Red",
      "Blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What cockpit structure helps shield a driver’s head from flying debris?",
    "correctAnswer": "HALO",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Helmet",
      "HANS",
      "Windscreen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "In which country are the majority of current F1 team headquarters located?",
    "correctAnswer": "United Kingdom",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Italy",
      "Austria",
      "United States"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "In what year did F1 stop awarding a bonus point for the fastest lap of the race?",
    "correctAnswer": "2025",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2022",
      "2023",
      "2024"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which Brazilian driver is the first to compete in F1 full-time since Felipe Massa?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gabriel Bortoleto",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Franco Colapinto",
      "Alfa Romeo",
      "Juan Pablo Montoya"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver has a tattoo of his race number “14” on his back?",
    "correctAnswer": "Fernando Alonso",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lando Norris",
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Sergio Perez"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team is often associated with the phrase “Silver Arrows”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mercedes",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Aston Martin",
      "Haas",
      "Alpine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which famous F1 race is also part of the \"Triple Crown of Motorsport\"?",
    "correctAnswer": "Monaco GP",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Imola GP",
      "Spa GP",
      "Singapore GP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which country’s Grand Prix was held at the \"Österreichring\" track before it became the Red Bull Ring?",
    "correctAnswer": "Austria",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Hungary",
      "Netherlands",
      "Portugal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What year did Red Bull Racing Team make their Formula 1 debut?",
    "correctAnswer": "2005",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2003",
      "2007",
      "2010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver has the nickname ‘The Viking’?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kevin Magnussen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Nico Hulkenberg",
      "Valtteri Bottas",
      "Romain Grosjean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What number is permanently retired in honor of Jules Bianchi?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "29",
      "33",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver is known as the ‘Man Who Walked Out of the Fire”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Romain Grosjean",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jos Verstappen",
      "Niki Lauda",
      "Jo Siffert"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which circuit is known for the longest race ever (4 min, 39 sec)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Canadian GP",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "COTA GP (Texas)",
      "Silverstone GP (UK)",
      "Suzuka GP (Japan)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the standard pit-lane speed limit?",
    "correctAnswer": "50 mph",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "40 mph",
      "30 mph",
      "60 mph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which F1 driver was given the most grid drops ever (70) when all his penalty points were added up?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jenson Button",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      " Romain Grosjean",
      "Felipe Nasr",
      "Daniil Kvyat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 commentator drove for the Renault Sport F1 team from 2016-2018?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jolyon Palmer",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jenson Button",
      "Martin Brundle",
      "David Coulthard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which Formula 2 racing question below is NOT correct?",
    "correctAnswer": "F2 Championship winners always advance to F1 the following season",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All F2 cars are identical in design",
      "F2 races are always 60 minutes in length",
      "F2 is a testing ground for future F1 drivers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What type of engines do modern F1 cars use?",
    "correctAnswer": "V6 Turbo Hybrid",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "V12",
      "Diesel",
      "Electric only"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 team ran a sponsor-less car and black nose to mourn the 9/11 attacks?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ferrari",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Williams-BMW",
      "McLaren-Mercedes",
      "Jaguar-Cosworth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 3,
    "levelName": "Front Runner",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the highest number of pit stops in a single F1 race (across all drivers)?",
    "correctAnswer": "89",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "52",
      "63",
      "77"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which track is famous for a chaotic first corner and has a stadium section?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mexico",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Montreal",
      "US - COTA",
      "Barcelona"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "With which team did Ayrton Senna win his first championship title?",
    "correctAnswer": "McLaren",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ferrari",
      "Williams",
      "Lotus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver is known as ‘The Professor”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Alain Prost",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ayton Senna",
      "Michael Schumacher",
      "Robert Kubica"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What track is nicknamed ‘The Temple of Speed”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Monza",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jeddha",
      "Suzuka",
      "Spa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What constructor has won the most Constructor’s Championships?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ferrari",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "McLaren",
      "Williams",
      "Red Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver got their first F1 win at the 2020 Italian Grand Prix?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pierre Gasly",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Esteban Ocon",
      "Carlos Saintz",
      "Lance Stroll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which engine powered McLaren in 2015-2017?",
    "correctAnswer": "Honda",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Mercedes",
      "Williams",
      "Alpine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who was the first driver to win a race for Red Bull?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sebestian Vettel",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Mark Webber",
      "Daniel Ricciardo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Approximately how much lateral g-force can a driver experience under normal circumstances when cornering?",
    "correctAnswer": "6G",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "4G",
      "5G",
      "8G"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is Max Verstappen’s long-time race engineer?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gianpiero Lambiase ('GP')",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Peter Bonnington",
      "Bryan Bozzi",
      "John Howard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many of the current F1 races are held on street circuits?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many times has a F1 driver won a race after starting last?",
    "correctAnswer": "6 times",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "3 times",
      "4 times",
      "7 times"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the highest number of wins for any F1 driver?",
    "correctAnswer": "103",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "94",
      "97",
      "108"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who holds the record for the youngest F1 World Champion at the time of their first win?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Ayrton Senna",
      "George Russell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the typical number of F1 pit crew members per team?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "15",
      "25",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who holds the record (19) for the most wins in a single season?",
    "correctAnswer": "Max Verstappen ",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ayton Senna",
      "Michael Schumacher",
      "Lewis Hamilton"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the 75% rule in F1?",
    "correctAnswer": "If more than 75% of a scheduled race is completed, full points are awarded",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "If more than 75% of drivers complete a scheduled race, 75% of points are awarded",
      "Only 75% of total race points are awarded if 10 or more drivers fail to complete a scheduled race",
      "If more than 75% of drivers complete a scheduled race, full points are awarded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who was the youngest team principal to take the helm of an F1 race team?",
    "correctAnswer": " Christian Horner",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Toto Wolff",
      "Sir Frank Williams",
      "Andrea Stella"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What devise helps reduce head and neck injuries during crashes?",
    "correctAnswer": "HANS",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "HALO",
      "Seat Belt",
      "Cockpit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What year did Bernd Maylander begin driving the safety car at each F1 race?",
    "correctAnswer": "2000",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2005",
      "2010",
      "2015"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What special license is a qualification that allows a driver to compete in the FIA Formula One World Championship?",
    "correctAnswer": "Super license",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "International Drivers License",
      "Rally License",
      "Entrant's License"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the role of the 'lollipop man' during a pit stop?",
    "correctAnswer": "To signal the driver when it is safe to leave a pit stop",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "To signal the driver where to come to a halt for a pit stop",
      "To lift the car slightly so the tires can be removed",
      "To let the driver know the pit stop activities have been completed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How long does a F1 engine typically last?",
    "correctAnswer": "5 races",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "7 races",
      "10 races",
      "12 races"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which race in 2021 saw a one-lap restart with a standing start that controversially decided the championship?",
    "correctAnswer": "Abu Dhabi GP",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Monaco GP",
      "British GP",
      "Bahrain GP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is the Managing Director of the all female F1 Academy Series?",
    "correctAnswer": "Susie Wolff",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Claire Williams",
      "Hannah Schmitz",
      "Desire Wilson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver won the 1988 F1 World Championship with 15 poles and 18 race wins?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ayrton Senna",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Nelson Piquet",
      "Thierry Boutsen",
      "Alain Prost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team was disqualified from the 2007 Constructors' Championship due to a spying scandal?",
    "correctAnswer": "McLaren",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Mercedes",
      "Williams",
      "Ferrari"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which location hosted the first F1 night race in 2008?",
    "correctAnswer": "Singapore",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Monaco",
      "Las Vegas",
      "Qatar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is attached to an F1 car to keep it from running too low to the ground?",
    "correctAnswer": "Skid Block",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ride Sensor",
      "Aerodynamic Vent",
      "Tire Sensor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What F1 driver was notably caught speeding (off-track) in 1998?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nigel Mansell",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Eddie Irvine",
      "Jacques Villeneuve",
      "Ralf Schumacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver famously shouted \"leave me alone, I know what I’m doing\"?",
    "correctAnswer": " Kimi Räikkönen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Yuki Tsunoda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 track features a banked final corner?",
    "correctAnswer": "Netherlands (Zandvoort)",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Madrid (Madring)",
      "Malaysia (Sepang)",
      "GB (Silverstone)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which city’s street circuit includes the famous “Casino Square” and “Tunnel”?",
    "correctAnswer": "Monaco",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Las Vegas",
      "Miami",
      "Baku City"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which Formula 1 race features the iconic \"S Curves\" section at the start of the lap?",
    "correctAnswer": "Suzuka (Japan)",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Monza (Italy)",
      "Red Bull Ring (Austria)",
      "Bahrain International Circuit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the maximum number of power unit components (ICE, Turbo, MGU-H, MGU-K) a driver can use in a season without penalty?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who is the only F1 driver to have won a championship without winning a single race in the final season of his career?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nico Rosberg",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Pierre Gasly",
      "Fernando Alonso",
      "Jenson Button"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver earned the nickname “Crash Kid” from Mark Webber in 2010?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Felipe Massa",
      "Robert Kubica",
      "Bruno Senna"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team ran the infamous “six-wheeled” F1 car in the 1970s?",
    "correctAnswer": "Tyrrell",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lotus",
      "Benetton",
      "Ferrari"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is Autodromo Internazionale Enzo e Dino Ferrari also know as?",
    "correctAnswer": "Imola",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ferrari Headquarters",
      "The Autodrome",
      "Ferrari International Auto Museum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the highest number of rookie drivers to join a single F1 season?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who was the first F1 driver to be managed by Fernando Alonso's company, A14 Management?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gabriel Bortoleto",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Oliver Bearman",
      "Kimi Antonelli",
      "Isack Hadjar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 4,
    "levelName": "World Champion",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the highest number of retirements in a single F1 race (hint: 21 starters)",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "16",
      "14",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag signals a mechanical issue requiring return to the pit?",
    "correctAnswer": "Black with Orange Disc",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Yellow",
      "Red",
      "Blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What color flag indicates a deterioration in track grip (oil or water)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Yellow and Red Striped",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Orange and White Checkered",
      "Black and Blue Striped",
      "Blue and Yellow Checkered"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the maximum fuel limit (kg) for a race?",
    "correctAnswer": "110 kg",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "120 kg",
      "130 kg",
      "140 kg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver is the son of a MotoGP legend?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Doohan",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Liam Lawson",
      "Franco Colapinto",
      "Niki Lauda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Who is the longest serving team principal since F1 inception?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Frank Williams",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Fred Vasseur",
      "Flavio Briatore",
      "Christian Horner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which team was first to have a female team principal?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sauber",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Alpine",
      "Haas",
      "Williams"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who is considered the most famous F1 commentator of all time?",
    "correctAnswer": "Murray Walker",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Martin Brundle",
      "David Croft",
      "Ted Kravitz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What carbon fiber structure surrounds drivers as a safety capsule?",
    "correctAnswer": "Survival Cell",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "HALO",
      "Helmet",
      "Roll Bar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver led the push for mandatory seatbelts & helmets?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sir Jackie Stewart",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Niki Lauda",
      "Ayrton Senna",
      "Michael Schumacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "How many points must a driver collect to qualify for a F1 super license?",
    "correctAnswer": "40 points",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "25 pts",
      "30 pts",
      "50 pts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which driver holds the record for the most consecutive races finishes without retirement (27)?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lewis Hamilton",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Esteban Ocon",
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Michael Schumacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which F1 circuit has the most corners?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jeddah",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Austin (COTA) ",
      "Miami",
      "Singapore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "At the 1997 European GP, 3 drivers set identical lap times (1:21.072) - which driver was NOT one of them?",
    "correctAnswer": "David Coulthard",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jacques Villeneuve",
      "Michael Schumacher",
      "Heinz-Harald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which manufacturer last competed in F1 in 2009?",
    "correctAnswer": "BMW",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ford",
      "Porsche",
      "Jaguar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who was the first female race engineer in F1?",
    "correctAnswer": "Laura Muller",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Claire Williams",
      "Susie Wolff",
      "Hanna Schmitz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Slim Borgudd was a drummer for which band while also racing in F1?",
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Eagles",
      "The Cure",
      "Depeche Mode"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 driver famously pushed his car across the finish line in 1985?",
    "correctAnswer": "Thierry Boutsen",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Jackie Stewart",
      "Nigel Manson",
      "Alain Prost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the highest number of cars that ran out of fuel in a single race?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the approximate sound of a F1 car in decibels?",
    "correctAnswer": "130",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "140",
      "150",
      "160"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which F1 driver has raced for the most teams (14) over his career?",
    "correctAnswer": "Chris Amon",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Luca Badoer",
      "Ayrton Senna",
      "Andrea de Cesaris "
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What material previously used for track barriers was banned in 1967?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hay Bales",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Tire Barriers",
      "Sand Filled Drums",
      "Concrete Barriers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Who claimed the first “Triple Crown’ by winning in the Monaco GP, the 24 Hours of Le Mans, and the Indianapolis 500?",
    "correctAnswer": "Graham Hill",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Fernando Alonso",
      "Michael Schumacher",
      "Juan Pablo Montoya"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Which driver holds the record (24) for most consecutive front-row starts in Formula 1 history?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ayrton Senna",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Michael Schumacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "At which circuit did Ayrton Senna take his first F1 victory?",
    "correctAnswer": "Portuguese Grand Prix",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Austrian GP",
      "SPA ",
      "Spanish GP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What object does the Monaco GP require be welded down before each race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Manhole Covers",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Track Barriers",
      "Raised Curbs",
      "Starting Line Markers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which constructor entered F1, won a race in its debut season, and then never won again?",
    "correctAnswer": "Brawn GP",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Shadow Racing Cars",
      "EMKA Racing",
      "NISMO"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which famous race was part of the F1 World Championship calendar from 1950-1960?",
    "correctAnswer": "Indianapolis 500",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "24 Hours of Le Mans",
      "Targa Florio",
      "Carrera Panamericana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Approximately how many meters does it take for a F1 driver to break from 60 mpg to 0 mph?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "10",
      "20",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "Approximately what is the F1 record for leading the most racing miles in a single season from the front?",
    "correctAnswer": "3300 miles",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "2600 miles",
      "3900 miles",
      "4400 miles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which former F1 World Champion was once kidnapped before a race?",
    "correctAnswer": "Juan Manuel Fangio",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Ayrton Senna",
      "Jack Brabham",
      "Giuseppe Farina"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which country hosted the first F1 Grand Prix outside of Europe, in 1953?",
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Mexico",
      "Canada",
      "US"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "What is the purpose of F1's 107% rule?",
    "correctAnswer": "To prevent cars that drive to slowly from competing",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "To prevent tire pressure from being overinflated",
      "To ensure skid blocks are within mandate parameters",
      "To ensure a car is not more than 107% above the targeted weight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which race in 1997 saw a deliberate crash by Michael Schumacher to try to secure the championship?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jerez GP",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Austrian GP",
      "Hungarian GP",
      "Italian GP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the minimum thickness (when new) of an F1 car's skid block?",
    "correctAnswer": "10 mm",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "12 mm",
      "14m",
      "15 mm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which car component is used to send information to race control and the garage in real-time?",
    "correctAnswer": "Telemetry",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Aerodynamics",
      "Electronic Control Unit",
      "Sensors"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Name one of the two drivers who collided while leading the 2016 Spanish Grand Prix, taking each other out?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nico Rosberg",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Sebastian Vettel",
      "Valtteri Bottas",
      "Sergio Perez"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which driver was disqualified from the 2021 Hungarian Grand Prix for not having enough fuel for post-race sampling?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "George Russell",
      "Nicholas Latifi",
      "Lance Stroll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which famous F1 race ended in 2005 with only 6 cars starting due to tire safety concerns?",
    "correctAnswer": "USGP (Indianapolis)",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "British GP (Silverstone)",
      "Mexico City GP",
      "Austrian GP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which F1 support team member won an Olympic medal in rowing?",
    "correctAnswer": "Tom Stallard",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Bernie Collins",
      "Alessandro Fisaro",
      "Adrian Newey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fluid",
    "question": "What is the fastest top speed ever recorded during an official F1 race weekend?",
    "correctAnswer": "231 mph",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "226 mph",
      "214 mph",
      "243 mph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelNumber": 5,
    "levelName": "Legend",
    "questionType": "Fixed",
    "question": "Which 21st century F1 driver won the 24 Hours of Le Mans race while actively competing in the F1 season?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nico Hulkenberg",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Robert Kubica",
      "Fernando Alonso",
      "Kamui Kobayashi"
    ]
  }
]